crmls.org 2015-06-07

# CRMLS Privacy Policy

## California Regional Multiple Listing Service, Inc.   
Privacy Policy

### About the Policy

California Regional Multiple Listing Service, Inc. ( "CRMLS") operates an online multiple listing service and serves real estate professionals throughout the state of California. CRMLS is committed to the protection and security of the information provided by the visitors to crmls.org (including its online and mobile versions) and homeseekers.com (including its online and mobile versions) (hereinafter "Websites").

### Application of Policy

This policy applies to the Websites and its associated pages. Please note that there may be links to other companies and websites on CRMLS' Websites that are not owned by CRMLS. With respect to those companies and websites, this policy is inapplicable.

### Types of Information Collected

When you visit the Websites, CRMLS collects certain information about your visit. For instance, CRMLS may collect information about the type of internet browser you are using, the server name and Internet Protocol address through which you access the Websites, the pages you access within the Websites, information about your geographic location, information you input into the Websites regarding your contact information or real estate listings, or if you navigated to the CRMLS Websites from another website, CRMLS may capture the internet address of where you came from.

CRMLS may have to disclose, transfer, sell, or assign information obtained from you through the Websites to a third party if CRMLS utilizes companies and individuals who CRMLS employs or engages to perform services on CRMLS� behalf for the Websites or if requested by the government, law enforcement, or via subpoena. CRMLS may also disclose information if CRMLS is or may be acquired by another entity or engages in the sale of CRMLS� assets.

### How CRMLS Protects Information

CRMLS takes appropriate measures to ensure that any information collected is protected. Please note, however, that due to the open nature of the internet, CRMLS cannot guarantee that all communication between you and CRMLS will be free from unauthorized access by third parties nor can we be responsible or liable for information harvested or scraped from the Websites by third parties.

### Cookies

The Websites utilize Cookie technology to assist CRMLS in keeping track of the pages you visit while on the Websites. Cookies are small bits of information that can be transferred to your computer to identify your computer�s browser. When you visit the Websites, CRMLS may place one or more cookies on your computer. The use of cookies helps CRMLS improve the quality of the services provided to you. At any time, you have the ability to adjust your internet browser�s settings to not accept cookies. If you choose to disable the cookies, however, there is a chance that certain features of the Websites will not operate properly. 

### Advertising

CRMLS utilizes advertisements in its Websites. CRMLS wants to make these advertisements useful and relevant to you. As a result, CRMLS may provide advertisements on the Websites based on information collected from you or in relation to your interaction with the Websites. The advertisers may utilize Cookies and other technologies to your online activity and to learn what types of information are of most interest to you. Use of these technologies by the advertisers is subject to the advertisers� own privacy policies.

### Children

This Website is not directed to children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect any information, including personal information, from children under the age of 13.

### Policy Changes

CRMLS reserves the right to change or amend this Privacy Policy at any time with or without notice to you. 

### Comments and Questions

If you have any comments or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by clicking here or by mail at: 

legal@crmls.org  
California Regional Multiple Listing Service, Inc.  
Attn: Legal Department  
180 Via Verde, Suite 200  
San Dimas, CA 91773  
(909) 859-2040
